Coming December 22nd!
First, Sendai!
We are the U.X.L. team!
Thank you for your cooperation!
The road is still long
If you can turn around at the end of
your breath
Today is the first day of the live
house tour, Seinai Park!
It's going to start in a few seconds
That's right!
I can't stop!
Everyone's movie
Yes!
It's summer, so let's have a hot and
juicy live like a beef tongue today!
Yes!
Let's do our best!
I'm so nervous.
OK.
Let's calm down.
Let's do our best.
Kanonmi!
Hitoka!
Haruka!
Juni!
Hiyori!
Tokimeki Tendenbu!
KUROKURO!
Thank you all for coming today.
Go! Go! Go! Go!
At the Night Princess Princess,
BAN-chan took a picture!
Oh!
I took it!
Do you remember, everyone?
You remember, right?
You want to see it, right?
Can you see it? Can you show it?
Oh!
I'll talk about that later.
My bangs look OK.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Say something!
Let's take a picture!
Thank you for coming!
It was fun!
See you tomorrow!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you for your hard work.
Bye bye.
We started the 19th.
Today was Sendai.
It was a big turn.
It was fun.
It was a great rush.
It was like, wow.
But we did a lot.
We did.
We challenged a lot.
Today was a great day.
It was the first time for everyone.
We were excited.
Yes.
Tomorrow is Osaka.
We'll do our best.
Next is Osaka.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Kanami!
Wondy!
Futoka!
Haruka!
Sumiya!
Iori!
Tokimeki Sendenbu!
Rakkan!
Um...
Test, test, test, test.
Yes!
Tokimeki Kase Housouin!
On this tour, I'm Haruka Koizumi, in
charge of the Otsu-Ama-Yubi!
Thank you!
Osaka Park, are you ready to have fun?
Girls, are you ready to have fun?
Yes!
It's important, it's important
We are living in the middle of now
We need love words, we need them
Let's go!
Go! Go! Go!
Touch, touch, touch, touch, touch,
touch, touch, touch
We're going to lose
When Hitoka starts using the parasol,
everyone starts using it
When you know you're hungry, you start
exercising
Tokimeki Senzenbu is a simple group
that is easy to be influenced
Is this a broadcast?
Yes, it is
Hitoka started using the parasol first
this year
Then she started using it the next day
How about Julia?
She started using it the next day
She looked like this, or she suddenly
said,
I'm going to use the parasol in the
summer
I'm going to use the parasol
I talked to her and she said she
started using it when she was in first
grade
Really?
That's elegant
Thank you
I'm going to be myself, I'm going to be
you
Listen to our feelings so you don't
regret it
I'm Tsushina Kanami
I fell in love with you
So, can you accept my love like
takoyaki?
Can I really be myself?
I don't like the face of Neoki
Please make it your only love
sightseeing spot
This was Tokimeki Senzenbu
Thank you very much
I'm Haruka Koizumi, the host of this
tour.
Everyone, finally,
Rock Roya!
Thank you!
Next is Nagoya.
I love you!
We are Tokimeki Senzenbu.
Thank you for your support.
Tokimeki Senzenbu Rock On!
Are you excited?
Thank you.
Let's enjoy together.
We are going to read a message from
Haruka Koizumi.
I love having Kanami massage my
shoulder blades.
Is that all?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
This is the first time I've heard this
short message.
What is this? Is this an announcement?
This is a message from Haruka Koizumi.
I love having Kanami massage my
shoulder blades.
What should I do?
She read the message.
Yuno, Baki, Kanami, Kouko, and us.
We are the ones who are loved by
everyone.
Thank you very much!
Did you enjoy the live?
See you again!
Thank you!
We did it!
We finished the performance!
Yay!
It was fun!
Thank you!
Nagoya is the best!
Bambi is also doing well!
What is this?
Tarakota!
Next, Fukuoka!
The last one is Fukuoka.
Thank you.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Hiyoi Yoshikawa, the visual
director of the Fudo center,
which is a broadcast station of
Sekimeki.
Yoshikawa?
I'm Hiyoi.
I'm going to start the show soon.
This time, I'm going to introduce the
new program,
which is going to be broadcast soon.
I'm in charge of visual.
Visual?
I'll do my best to show you a lot of
cute things.
Let's start the engine.
Sekimeki Broadcast, Knock On!
I'm going to the 30th floor.
I hope the venue is warm.
Thank you.
It's simple anyway and you want to fly
Thank you very much.
So,
Kimi no Heart ni Rock on!
We are DOKIMEKI SENDEIMU.
Thank you very much.
I want to dance with you.
It was so fun.
It was so fast.
I want to calm down.
It was so fun.
I love you all.
Bye-bye.
It's over.
Thank you very much.
It was so fast.
I'm glad to be here.
We will do our best.
Thank you very much.
I love you.
Bye-bye.
Please subscribe to this channel.
The last rap!
You're a youth hacker, right?
This love is a pain in the ass, but
it's the best
I don't care if I'm a loser
Because I fell in love with you
I'm looking forward to it!
High-Five!
If you're feeling down, then come with
me
One, two, three
We can overcome anything
Go! To the future!
Is everyone okay?
Wait a minute!
I didn't!
I'm glad that everyone is so funny,
so I can work hard on the day of the
competition.
I'm off to make my final shots!